Translated by Releska
The sky of the blue sea
The sky of the purple sea
It is all about love
It is always you
Indeed
Because it is the opposite of the universe
If you are so happy
Tears are not enough
It's been a long time since I saw you
I'm sure your smile will come true
You and you, you and you
If you love me, if you love me
I'm sure you'll be able to see me
It's open
I even know the current situation
What is going on here?
I can't wait to see my return
But there's nothing to be regretful
I was so happy to be with Muka Muka, and I was so happy to be with Muka Muka!
Muka Muka, Aozura Kyo Shitsu!
Oh, no, Shoya V-tari Shitsu!
Oh, Muka! It's hot, isn't it?
I made a lot of things in elementary school.
It's hot, isn't it?
You're studying right now, aren't you?
It's a test, isn't it?
Is it a test for studying?
I thought it would be nice if I went to school every day.
But if I had to go, it would be nice for me to go.
Well, it's not that bad.
We were in this classroom for a while.
I did it!
Muka Muka, look at this!
Sorry!
I want to go to school.
I want to go to the teacher, too.
Teacher?
If you want to go to the teacher, I'll go.
Really?
Yes.
It's always a demo, isn't it?
No, it's not. The teacher will go to school.
I want to go to school, too.
Go to school? Are you doing school?
Yes!
Go to school!
I'll go to school from now on.
I want to go to school, too.
It's really cool!
There was something like this in this island.
It's a pretty good school.
It's a pretty good school, so it's not hard to fight.
But I don't think the teacher will be able to go to school.
Is that so?
Are you going to school, too?
I like school!
Where is the teacher?
There is a teacher, but it's not there.
What are you saying?
There is a school, but it's not.
I don't know.
What?
Did you have a school?
No, it's not. It's a pretty good school.
It's a pretty good school.
What kind of teacher is there?
It's like a teacher, isn't it?
I didn't have a teacher.
Are you going to school at night?
I wonder if everyone would be able to go to school.
That's good.
I was in the middle of the school when I came here.
You have to go to school, too.
I don't know.
What are you saying?
You're going to school, and you're going to school.
I don't know what kind of teacher is.
I'm going to school like a teacher.
I'm not saying.
I'm going to school.
I'm going to school like a teacher, and I'm going to school like a teacher.
That's right.
I might be scared of my teacher's birthday.
What kind of teacher is that?
That's right. I'm going to look for a teacher.
That's right.
What kind of teacher is that?
There's a teacher.
I like school like a teacher.
I'm going to school like a teacher.
What?
Is it delicious?
Yes, it's delicious.
I'm going to eat something delicious in the shop.
That's good.
Hey, are you going to school now?
I'm going to school.
There's a teacher who's going to read the book.
This is a really good school.
There's no teacher in the school, so I'm going to school tomorrow.
Stop!
Maid, are you going to school?
I want to listen to school.
But listen to me. I like school so much.
Hey, are you going to school?
Grama?
It's not like that.
Hey, what kind of teacher is that?
I don't know a lot of teachers.
There's a lot of teachers.
I'm looking forward to it.
I told you.
The teacher who was in the school was also in the school.
He was in the school?
School?
Are you going to school in the school?
That's right.
I'm going to school.
The teacher is going to school.
I'm not a child.
I'm going to school.
Are you going to school in the school?
That's right.
Everyone wants to see the school.
I'm not going to school.
I'm going to school.
I'm going to school today.
Ah, this is it.
I'm going to school.
I'm going to school today.
What kind of teacher is that?
What does a lot of teachers say?
There's no way to explain it.
There's a lot of teachers.
What is it?
I don't know if I can explain it.
School?
That's right.
The teacher who was in the school was in the school.
I see.
There's no way to explain it.
The teacher who was in the school was in the school.
The teacher who was in the school.
I see.
I know it.
There's no way to explain it.
That's right.
We may see the school.
If you find a suitable teacher, you'll know soon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got it.
Then I'll sleep now.
The swimming pool is a place where you can swim.
Ah!
Yay!
Kakoro-kun!
The school is starting.
What?
The school?
It's the beginning.
The school is starting.
What?
Do you want to go to school?
What school?
I'll go too!
What?
Me too!
I'm going too!
Hey! You're here!
Wait! I'll go too!
Alright, let's go to the gym.
Let's go to the gym.
Now, let's go to the gym.
Okay!
I wonder if it's going to start soon.
I'm looking forward to it.
What kind of teacher is this?
Teacher!
What's the teacher?
I thought it was like this.
Who is this?
The teacher said it was a teacher.
It's a teacher.
You can't do anything without the teacher.
The teacher said it was a teacher.
I'm going to start.
The school is starting.
I'll introduce myself.
I'm a teacher of the school.
It's a student.
The student of the student of the school.
Ah, it's a habit.
She's not so normal to be morejalishly friendly than people in Uki-derm.
I'm going to start the school.
I have an interview from an elementary school teacher.
You have an interview!
I'll be working hard.
Oh...
You have an interview!
I'm going to be an instructor!
I'm going to pay you back!
It won't be hard even if your school registration is done.
It'll be me too.
What?
It's a lunch box.
I see. It's said that it's Chien's symbol from now on.
Please get out of here!
It's been a long time since I saw you.
Oh, I see. I'm glad to see you.
Please!
Ho ho ho! I'm going to start my job.
Yes!
Then, I'm going to start my job.
I'm going to start my job.
You're getting the teacher right.
Isn't this the atmosphere?
Lord Kami-sama, please introduce yourself.
Please do your best.
I'll do my best.
The teacher of Kojikoji!
Oh, good!
This is Moji-guji Sensei. I'm coming!
The date I'm planning on today's mission is to teach you five times.
Five times? What are you talking about?
1, 2, 3, 5, 2, 3, 5, 2, 1.
We have to do that together.
1, 2, 3, 5, 2, 1, 3, 2, 1.
1123-213
If you don't find it, I'll get you a blue hat.
You see?
I'll get you a blue hat if you tell me something.
If I tell you this, I'll get you a blue hat.
I do that because it's wonderful.
I want to tell you who's the one who's the one who's the one whose name is the one.
This is probably the one.
Wow, so much fun.
I'll change theuplet school!
Let's do it!
I can't do anything I love about these stupid girls!
Please don't do it!
Don't take any Morebunny to this school right away!
I'm not telling you to turn the classroom into a Cup of Music!
Go and learn from these guys!
Yeah.
It's time not to get any older University's students to be!
Let's wait until the school becomes school-abduced.
C'mon!
Don't do it!
This isn't the bottom line!
I don't get it! I don't get it, but I'm a teacher!
Are you a teacher?
Yes, I am a teacher!
I'll teach you guys a lesson, right?
Yes, I'm a teacher!
I'm a teacher!
. I'm a teacher!
Don't cry!
I'm going to grow up for the best.
I'm a teacher!
My teacher is a teacher!
A teacher.
Oh, I see. This is the end of the game.
Oh, I still don't want to go back?
Why?
I'm sure Mr. Ko-cho has decided to do it.
I don't want to go back.
Then, Mr. Kiro, please raise your blue hair.
Mr. Ko-cho, please raise your blue hair.
Yes, Mr. Kiro, please raise your blue hair.
What? I'm Mr. Ko-cho?
When Mr. Ko-cho was in the air,
Mr. Kiro would have decided to do it.
I'm Mr. Kiro, too.
It's not a good thing, Mr. Kiro.
I don't want to go back to the air,
but I don't want to go back.
I'm not going to say such things.
I'm going to go back to the air, Mr. Kiro.
I don't want to go back to the air, Mr. Kiro.
I'm going to do it, Mr. Ko-cho.
Then, I'll teach you how to do it.
If you do it like this,
you'll understand how to use your legs.
Mr. Kiro!
Mr. Kiro, you're doing great!
Yes, Mr. Kiro.
You're doing great, Mr. Kiro.
I see.
You're doing great.
Mr. Kiro, please raise your blue hair.
No, I'm not.
I'm not going to go back to the air,
but I'm not going to go back to the air.
Oh, no.
No, I'm not going to go back to the air,
I'm not going back to the air.
I'm not going to go back to the air.
You're attacking me a lot today.
Are you surprised?
You were really as surprised.
I can't go to such a place like that.
Is it a name?
Is there any school in the morning?
I don't even have an instrument.
Kiii, it's a school!
Today too.
It's a bit late, isn't it?
We don't have a relationship.
Let's go, my friends.
It's not good, Rokkun.
If you see the blue wind,
why don't you put something on it?
Oh, I see.
The kids are going to school.
Dad?
Don't say that.
It's a job.
It's a nice job.
Oh, that's right.
It's a job.
I don't know if you've heard of it.
It's cute.
It's great.
I respect your heart.
I like you.
Rokkun.
Put your hands on it.
Everyone, go to school.
I won't teach you anything today.
What do you want me to teach you?
I saw it in the world where you taught me how to run.
Hey, everyone, come to school.
I'll teach you.
Don't teach me.
I don't want to teach you anything.
Huh?
What?
You're so dirty.
It's a bit strange.
I can't teach you anything today.
Wow.
Mr. Rokkun.
Huh?
Mr. Rokkun...
Mr. Rokkun.
Hey.
Will you teach me the next day?
No, I won't.
Let's go!
How are we going to do that?
If we don't do that, what's the end of today's class?
Oh, yeah.
This is a battle!
Are you there?
I can't do anything without you.
But, I can't do anything without you.
That's right.
Ueiba,
you can't do anything!
You want to get rid of it, so...
That's right!
Hey, teach me the special chock-chock!
Look, chock-chock!
Chock-chock!
Ah!
You've been waiting all the time, Kii!
You've become so sleepy!
Kii! Kii! Kii!
You're a little bit...
I'm a little bit hungry!
Mika Mika, please do something.
What do you think about it?
You and Ms. Kouli are the same age as Ms. Kouli, aren't you?
Me?
I'm the one who's always in front of Ms. Kouli's parents.
That's right!
Ms. Kouli's parents are the same age as Ms. Kouli's parents!
And Ms. Kouli's parents are the same age as Ms. Kouli's parents!
I got it.
Ms. Kouli's parents are the same age as Ms. Kouli's parents.
Then, what do you want me to tell you?
That's...
What do you want me to tell you?
Hurry up!
I don't want to tell you anything.
You can't do anything!
That's right!
Get ready!
Now!
I'm so excited!
Huh?
What do you want me to tell you?
Is there any other way?
I'm so excited!
I can't do this!
Next, I'll tell you what I want you to tell me.
It's difficult.
I can't do this!
I'm so excited!
If you want to solve this game, I'm so excited!
I can't do it!
Farewell.
What's that?
I can't fool you with using aissors.
If I use that, I can't fool you with using windscreen.
Translated by Releska
Because I'm a hot girl
Fire fire fire fire everybody
Shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake
Shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake-
It's fun and fun
I'm calling you boys
Translated by Releska